<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LEGO Sets and MOCs on Emma Sax</title>
    <link>https://emmasax.com/interests-and-hobbies/lego/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LEGO Sets and MOCs on Emma Sax</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:49:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://emmasax.com/interests-and-hobbies/lego/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wildflower Bouquet (10313)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 19:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This set was made up of pretty much small pieces, not very many big pieces hanging out here. Personally, I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of such tiny pieces going together to make bigger items, but it was definitely interesting to see newer pieces and more fun ways to connect the pieces together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The colors were fun and bright, and the different flowers created were all unique. After all the individual flowers were put together, I used rubber bands to tie them all together (like a real bouquet), and then wrapped ribbon around the rubber bands. This way they don&amp;rsquo;t need to sit in a jar or vase in order to stay together.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunar New Year Traditions (80108)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I received this Lunar New Year LEGO set as a birthday gift, and I loved putting it together. Because it was modular, it allowed me and a friend to both put pieces together without interfering with the other person. I especially loved putting this set together because it allowed me to learn more about Lunar New Year traditions for myself, and gave me an opportunity to celebrate a traditional holiday to my native ethnicity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonsai Tree (10281)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I received this Bonsai Tree as a gift, and I absolutely loved putting it together. It was a great activity to do while stuck inside recovering from Covid. Putting the branches and pink leaves on the trees was a little tiresome and repetitive after a while, but it was relaxing and didn&amp;rsquo;t take much brain power.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I put the green leaves together as well, but ended up putting the pink on the tree itself. I&amp;rsquo;d love to design another base and tree trunk so I could put my green leaves on that and have both of them side by side, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten a chance to do that yet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Double Dorm Suite</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 20:25:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This dorm suite was designed after the suites that I lived at my senior year of the college. The idea is that multiple students each have their own bedroom, and they share a bathroom and common room together. In this version, each student has a TV, bed, desk, wardrobe, and chest. And in the common room, they have another TV, big wrap-around sofa, and a coffee table. The bathroom has a bathtub and shower, toilet, sink, and a washer/dryer. In college, we didn&amp;rsquo;t have our own laundry, but in this version, a laundry machine fit nicely.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Single Dorm Room</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 19:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Based on both of the previous dorm room types, this one is for a student who wishes to live alone. They have a little couch and coffee table, along with a full bathroom, and washer/dryer. They also have a full bedroom as well, but it&amp;rsquo;s all within the same main room, so it&amp;rsquo;s basically a little studio apartment without a kitchen. It&amp;rsquo;s vents are realistic, and contains two doors. However, there are no windows, which isn&amp;rsquo;t particularly realistic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Townhouse Toy Store 3-in-1 (31105)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This 3-in-1 Toy Store was such a joy to put together. I put together all 3 sets, starting with the Flower and Cake Shops, and ending with the Toy Store. Each of the sets was fun to put together, and it was fascinating to see how the designers used the same pieces in different ways. In fact, the most enjoyable thing about all of these sets is the variety of the buildings and pieces. It was enjoyable to put all of the sets together, a great way to spend an afternoon, and this set was absolutely worth the time and cost.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charles Dickens Tribute (40410)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got this Charles Dickens Tribute set as a free extra set from spending a certain amount of money at the LEGO store. I&amp;rsquo;m not normally a Charles Dickens or a &lt;em&gt;Christmas Carol&lt;/em&gt; fan, so normally, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t spend any money on this type of set. But putting it together was actually an absolute joy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was fun watching the book go from a wobbly frame to something sturdy, and the little room had lots of details with stickers and everything. I love how each of the minifigures have at least one stud to stand on, and the inside of the room is completely lined with tiles, meaning the floor is completely flat. As a bonus, the entire finished set still fits inside the original box, making it a perfect little gift for the holidays!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat 3-in-1 (30574)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 13:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was so excited when I saw that one of the freebies at the LEGO store was a little cat! It was also a 3-in-1, so it also came with an ostrich option and a cute little crab option. I put all three designs together to see which ones I liked the most.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The crab was by far the cutest. Its claws were a stretch, but I do have to give the designer credit for being able to come up with so many designs with so few pieces. The ostrich was impressive, essentially considering &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; it used all of the LEGO pieces. The cat&amp;hellip;. well, I think it may be the ugliest LEGO cat I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. It was very disappointing. The way my partner described it was that this set was designed by somebody who &lt;em&gt;hates&lt;/em&gt; cats and was just forced to make one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkie Kid (30341)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 12:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In normal circumstances, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t purchase any LEGO sets from &lt;em&gt;Monkie Kid&lt;/em&gt;. I&amp;rsquo;m not even entirely sure what it is&amp;hellip; maybe a TV show or movie brand or something? We received the set as a LEGO freebie when making another LEGO purchase. However, I found it was actually pretty enjoyable to put together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Putting together the little motorcycle was fun, and the minifigure&amp;rsquo;s facial expressions are definitely worth it. All-in-all, it was a fun little 10 minutes to spend doing LEGO. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t spend any actual money on this set though.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Double Dorm Room</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 09:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This dorm room is designed to be a home for two students, and also contains a combination washer/dryer and a full bathroom with a large sink/vanity, toilet, bathtub, and shower. It&amp;rsquo;s vents are realistic, and contains two doors. However, there are no windows, which isn&amp;rsquo;t particularly realistic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In terms of the LEGO aspect, the room&amp;rsquo;s walls are made of about 135 pieces. The two beds, desks, chairs, and armoires are completely identical, so no one student gets more furniture than any other. Viewers need to use their imagination for the armoires; I didn&amp;rsquo;t create them with doors, but the idea is that there&amp;rsquo;s a rod, and minifigures can hang up their clothes. There&amp;rsquo;s one chest per student to keep their belongings in as well. Lastly, my original design wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have put in a door with windows, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to find the ideal door on LEGO to purchase, so I used what I had in stock and colored the door black.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Princess Storybook Adventures (43174, 43175, 43176, 43177)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 19:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At first glance, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t interested in these LEGO sets because the minifigures are a different design. But after I realized they had a &lt;em&gt;Mulan&lt;/em&gt; set (she&amp;rsquo;s my favorite because she&amp;rsquo;s Chinese), I realized that I should give it a chance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I started with just that one box. I actually really liked it. I liked how the entire set collapses into this latching book for easy moving around. I think the minifigures are actually really cute, and as much as I hate putting stickers on, I like how customizable the stickers make the set.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raft</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 19:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This cute little raft was made from pieces that I found in my LEGO piece stash. The raft is LEGO piece #75977, and is found in many LEGO sets, as shown &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bricklink.com/v2/catalog/catalogitem.page?P=30086c01&#34;&gt;in BrickLink&lt;/a&gt;. The oars are piece #2542, and can also be found in many LEGO sets, as shown &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bricklink.com/catalogItemIn.asp?P=2542&amp;amp;in=S&#34;&gt;in BrickLink&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be surprised if they overlap.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The minifigures were designed by myself, and I specifically ordered top, bottom, face, and hair pieces of each minifigure (named Ben and Olivia). The chain is the finishing touch, and allows the raft to be hooked up to a dock.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unikitty Roller Coaster Wagon (30406)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 19:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think my partner and I received this set for free when we made some purchase over $45 or something at the LEGO store. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have purchased it otherwise, simply because I had never even heard of Unikitty before.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, it was a fun little set to put together. The wagon actually rolls, and it really shoots out little pieces as it goes. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty fun and cute, and Unikitty is adorable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flower Display (40187)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 19:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In my recent newfound LEGO phase, this was one of the first little sets that I did. When I put it together, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t aware of what LEGO would turn into in my life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My partner had the inkling that I would enjoy LEGO since he saw me enjoy putting together Ikea furniture. So, he wanted to get me a little test set, to see if I liked it. This is what he started with. It&amp;rsquo;s cute and fun, but the rose is a bit top-heavy, and so it falls over a lot. It&amp;rsquo;s actually fallen over so many times that eventually I lost the little leaf when it fell on the backside of a heavy piece of furniture. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll find it again when I move next.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Pack – Fun Fair (60234)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I originally got this set because it had a lot of minifigures. As any of my readers of my LEGO creations can tell, I love my minifigures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But as I was putting together this set, I realized that it came with a lot of intricate parts. All of the fairground games are actually usable (granted on a really small scale). The game where you hit the platform with a mallot to raise the ball to the bell at the top really works if you bop it with a little oomf. The event where you shoot down the targets works with the little toy shooter. And the duck-ring toss really spins! I&amp;rsquo;m very impressed, not just with the minifigures, but with the details in the set design as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Quad Dorm Room and Lounge</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 09:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This dormitory room is designed as a mixture between a college dorm room and a Harry Potter style common room. It is designed to be a home for four students, and contains two couches, chairs, and a coffee table for the students to talk and study. It has huge windows on one side of the room, to let in plenty of natural light.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In terms of the LEGO aspect, the room&amp;rsquo;s walls are made of about 175 pieces. The four beds, desks, chairs, and armoires are completely identical, so no one student gets more furniture than any other. Viewers need to use their imagination for the armoires; I didn&amp;rsquo;t create them with doors, but the idea is that there&amp;rsquo;s a rod, and minifigures can hang up their clothes. There&amp;rsquo;s lots of chests for the students to keep their belongings in as well. Each student has a backpack, too. Lastly, my original design wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have put in a door with windows, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to find the ideal door on LEGO to purchase, so I used what I had in stock and colored the door black.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Seater Car</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This 163 brick piece creates a one-of-a-kind minifigure-sized car. This car is unique in LEGO land because it can seat four LEGO minifigures at once; two in the front seat, and two in the backseat. Most LEGO cars for purchase only can seat one or two minifigures, one right behind each other. The roof is removable, so you can have easy access to the inside of the car. However, the car isn&amp;rsquo;t too realistic—the wheels don&amp;rsquo;t turn left/right. Lastly, although there is no trunk or frunk, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of room in the main part of the car for your minifigure&amp;rsquo;s accessories.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving Yacht (60221)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This diving yacht didn&amp;rsquo;t have long instructions, and was enjoyable to put together. It didn&amp;rsquo;t have lots of small pieces to attach, since the main boat was just one big piece. However, there were a lot of stickers. In general, given the price, this set was a worthwhile purchase, and a joy to put together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a link to the set: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lego.com/en-us/product/diving-yacht-60221&#34;&gt;Diving Yacht (60221)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;text-center photoswipe-gallery&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49977811291_ddb1464984_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;2048&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;1536&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49977811291_ddb1464984_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;200&#34; alt=&#34;Yacht with cover&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Yacht with cover&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978073062_941dcf47c0_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;2048&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;1536&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978073062_941dcf47c0_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;200&#34; alt=&#34;Scuba diver underwater&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Scuba diver underwater&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49977291103_ef9e709552_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;1536&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;2048&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49977291103_ef9e709552_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;200&#34; alt=&#34;Yacht with top off&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Yacht with top off&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978072787_1a3a6f42eb_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;2048&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;1536&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978072787_1a3a6f42eb_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;200&#34; alt=&#34;Two scuba divers underwater&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Two scuba divers underwater&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOTS Picture Frame (41914)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At first, I was a bit skeptical about these DOTS sets. How am I supposed to make sure that my design looks good? So I started off by copying one of the example pictures, but soon realized that with DOTS, everything you&amp;rsquo;d make looks just fine! There&amp;rsquo;s no way to go wrong with DOTS; they provide space for creativity and flexibility, giving plenty of ways to let out our inner kid!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helicopter Adventure 3-in-1 (31092)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This fun 3-in-1 is a joy to use. All of the sets are simple to follow, and each one maybe only takes about 15 minutes to put together, making it a short and enjoyable way to pass the time. I&amp;rsquo;d highly recommend any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a link to the set: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lego.com/en-us/product/helicopter-adventure-31092&#34;&gt;Helicopter Adventure (31092)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;text-center photoswipe-gallery&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49977843728_9fc00bb86e_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;2048&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;1536&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49977843728_9fc00bb86e_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;150&#34; alt=&#34;Helicopter front&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Helicopter front&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978363246_77d3d3a753_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;2048&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;1536&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978363246_77d3d3a753_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;150&#34; alt=&#34;Helicopter back&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Helicopter back&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978363141_99b96ba922_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;2048&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;1536&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978363141_99b96ba922_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;150&#34; alt=&#34;Steamboat front&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Steamboat front&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978362646_a50bd0f186_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;1536&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;2048&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978362646_a50bd0f186_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;150&#34; alt=&#34;Steamboat back&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Steamboat back&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978623487_2fa36eec74_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;2048&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;1536&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978623487_2fa36eec74_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;150&#34; alt=&#34;Plane front&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Plane front&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978362526_df871ac79c_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;1536&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;2048&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49978362526_df871ac79c_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;150&#34; alt=&#34;Plane back&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Plane back&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Box</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This little box (10 studs by 9 studs) is the ideal size for keeping personal items on the go. It can be used as a jewelry box, storage for other small LEGO pieces, or a place to keep headphones and short cords while traveling. It&amp;rsquo;s extremely durable and portable. Although my digital designer didn&amp;rsquo;t quite have all of the colors I&amp;rsquo;d like to use, the design is flexible, so you can use whatever color pieces you have in your storage bins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagon Alley (75978)</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m entering this small little Diagon Alley set as a separate entry from the Featured Harry Potter sets because this one is on a much smaller scale. While the majority of LEGO sets are what&amp;rsquo;s called mini scale, this one below is &lt;em&gt;micro&lt;/em&gt; scale, meaning it&amp;rsquo;s even smaller!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the link to the set: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lego.com/en-us/product/diagon-alley-75978&#34;&gt;Diagon Alley (75978)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;text-center photoswipe-gallery&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;photoswipe photo&#34; href=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/51787814383_df7ce71fd3_k.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;      data-pswp-width=&#34;2048&#34; data-pswp-height=&#34;1536&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;image&#34; src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/51787814383_df7ce71fd3_k.jpg&#34;  height=&#34;250&#34; alt=&#34;Micro scale Diagon Alley with Gringotts&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;invisible caption&#34;&gt;Micro scale Diagon Alley with Gringotts&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the very first sets that I started putting together recently (the one that I attribute this entire LEGO phase to) are the newest editions of the &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; sets. It started when my partner purchased the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lego.com/en-us/product/quidditch-match-75956&#34;&gt;Quidditch Match (75956)&lt;/a&gt; LEGO set for me for my birthday, and from there, it turned into a whole thing. Now, I have every &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; set that has come out since 2018, and I have a massive collection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
